Guide to the Robin Williams papers,1954-1997
Williams, Robin papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robin Williams papers, 1954-1997
14-25-3646
Robin Murphy Williams
1 cubic foot.
Correspondence, Photographs, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes biographical material, correspondence, photographs, and papers related to various symposiums.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor Emeritus of Social Science, Cornell University, 1946-2003.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes biographical material, correspondence, photographs, and papers related to various symposiums.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Williams, Robin Murphy.; Cornell University--Faculty.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.Dept. of Sociology.
Subjects:
Sociology.; Social ethics.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Biographical Material (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Photographs of Williams, 1980s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Publications by Williams, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Publications Annotated by Williams, 1956-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "The Social Sciences and the World of Tomorrow"-report on the Social Sciences at Cornell-Robin Williams chair, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Womens Roles Proposal, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Womens Roles-Award letter, correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Womens Roles-Plans for the project, letters,draft proposal, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Womens Roles-Correspondence with researchers, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Womens Roles-Financial records, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Womens Roles-Correspondence-Commission on the Education of Women, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Women's Roles-First person to use the data, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Nursing Profession-Progress report-Robin Williams, principal investigator, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Symposium-"Unanticipated Consequences of Social Structure" - honoring Robin Williams, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Symposium-"Games, Social Cooperation and War"-honoring Robin Williams, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Symposium honoring Robin Williams, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Symposium-Planning Materials, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Symposium-Pre-planning material, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Symposium-Publicity, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Symposium-letters from guests, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Symposium-book published as a result-"A nation divided:Diversity, Inequality and Community in American Society", 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Symposium-Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Symposium-Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Symposium-Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Symposium-Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- "Reflections on the life of Robin Williams" by Peter Rose-Smith College, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Speech in Seattle, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Response by Robin Williams, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Papers Prepared for Symposia, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Reprints by Williams on Pitirim Sorokin and Talcott Parsons, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)